tutsnare.com 2016-06-29

# privacy

**What information do we collect?**  
We collect information from you subscribe to our newsletter, fill out a form or comment on the site. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy..

**Information uses for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

To personalize your experience : (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

To improve our website : (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

To send periodic emails : The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

**Cookie Policy**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

**Disclose Policy**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**  
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include to make your learning better. These link contain official websites articles link or any be any ads link.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Terms and Conditions**

**Email Address**

Email address mentioned in the comment form will always be use for privacy and never be used for spam or will be sold to anyone.

**Comments**

We love comments, but any comments which is abusive, spread hatred, racial or any way hurting anyone opinion will never be entertained. We keep our comments moderated to maintain the integrity of individuals. We keep all the rights to accept or reject the comments.

**Ads policy**

We use third party advertising company to serve advertisement. Some of them like adsense uses the DART cookie to serve advertisement based on user interest and previous interaction. Though user can always opt out of DARt cookie settings by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/).

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

This policy was added on 31/08/2015

**Contact Us** ****

 **

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the contact page.

**
